<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GOCON CANADA</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on GOCON CANADA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GoCon Canada, but why?! And who?</title>
      <link>/blog/gocon-who-and-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/gocon-who-and-why/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since the inception of GoCon Canada many folks reached out with questions about the event and organizers. So we thought why not answer these and a few others.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go speak - resources for potential speakers</title>
      <link>/blog/speaker-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/speaker-resources/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;columns&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;column&#34;&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      Alone, we can do so little; together, we can do so much
      &lt;br&gt;
      -Helen Keller
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;column has-text-centered&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;/img/mountie_gopher.png&#34; alt=&#34;mountie gopher&#34; width=&#34;140&#34; height=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Go programming language marked its ninth anniversary in 2018 since it was &lt;a href=&#34;https://opensource.googleblog.com/2009/11/hey-ho-lets-go.html&#34;&gt;first publicly announced&lt;/a&gt;. Both the language and the community took off  🛫, with no signs of slowing down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.golang.org/9years&#34;&gt;Nine years of Go&lt;/a&gt; for a brief reflection. Incredible, right?!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a newcomer, part of the core team, or a long time enthusiast, there is a role we all play to foster a community that welcomes new ideas and people in this complex and crazy field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GoCon Canada would like to do its part in helping all feel welcome and build a sense of community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this post..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;discuss a few reasons &lt;em&gt;potential&lt;/em&gt; speakers don&amp;rsquo;t submit proposals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;provide some of our favorite &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/speaker-resources/#resources-from-the-web&#34;&gt;resources from the web&lt;/a&gt; that relate to conference proposals and speaking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Go has become a critical tool in the arsenal of software development teams across Canada.
Rated the &amp;ldquo;Most promising programming language&amp;rdquo; of 2018 in a recent JetBrains survey, the language has grown by leaps and bounds in the last year. Communities from coast to coast have popped up to support the language, and it’s become clear that there’s a strong appetite for a conference that can bring everybody together.
Gocon Canada seeks to do just that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>All delegates, speakers, sponsors and volunteers at any this event are required to agree with the Go Community Code of Conduct.
Summary: Our conference will include people from many different backgrounds. Organizers are committed to providing a friendly, safe and welcoming environment for all, regardless of gender identity and expression, sexual orientation, disabilities, neurodiversity, physical appearance, body size, ethnicity, nationality, race, age, religion, or similar personal characteristics.
These are the values to which people attending this event should aspire:  Be friendly and welcoming Be patient  Remember that people have varying communication styles and that not everyone is using their native language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event schedule</title>
      <link>/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/schedule/</guid>
      <description>8:00 Registration  9:00 Opening  9:30 Peter Kieltyka  peterk   Peter Kieltyka  peterk  webrpc: a simpler way to write api services for modern Web apps Consequatur. Molestiae odit or non so veritatis yet aliquid rem. Reprehenderit vel. Nostrud. Numquam sint and dolore or adipisci yet perspiciatis ex mollit. Aute labore. Exercitation consequatur for quae for ullamco ullam. Ullam sed veritatis ratione. Officia pariatur for exercitation but odit yet eiusmod or enim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get your ticket!</title>
      <link>/tickets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tickets/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Sponsors</title>
      <link>/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>Platinum    CrowdRiff is a visual marketing platform that is tailor-made for marketing teams at destinations, museums, attractions and resorts. Hiring Senior Back-End Developer Senior Front-End Developer      Flybits helps banks address customer expectations for personalized experiences that meet their day-to-day needs and life goals. Our contextual recommendation engine transforms digital channels by delivering hyper-personalized products, services and content when their customers need it most.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speakers</title>
      <link>/speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/speakers/</guid>
      <description>Putting things in order is hard. So we iterated over a map (which as of Go 1.0 is unordered) and got..
List of speakers on the Go playground   webrpc: a simpler way to write api services for modern Web apps         Peter Kieltyka  peterk Chief architect behind Horizon Games. Having co-founded both NuLayer and Pressly, he&amp;#39;s passionate about creating awesome teams and powerful products.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>